Cup of coffee?
Thank you.
From around here?
Long time ago.
Things sure as hell
have changed, huh?
Well, things change.
Hey, why don't I just put a little
taste of whiskey in that coffee?
What do you say?
That's nice.
You just sit down
over there.
Relax. You make yourself at home.
I'll bring you the coffee.
Thank you.
What can I do
for you fellas?
You wanna do
something for me?
You can open
the cash register.
All right,
all right.
You just take it easy.
You should leave.
I thought I heard an echo.
Did you hear an echo?
Now.
What the hell
you gonna do, old man?
Drool on me?
Mother...
Where did you learn
to fight like that?
It was long ago.
What the hell
is this?
You read, please.
"To participate in a
test of skill and courage
"against the greatest fighters being
assembled from the four corners..."
I'm invited?
Hey, Georgie!
Yeah.
Get a load of this.
You know what to do.
Let's go, guys!
Let's go!
Come on!
Hey, clown boy.
Get off of my street.
Wait a minute.
Hey, Dubois.
What are you, sick in
the head or something?
Please. Grow up,
go get yourself some decent
clothes and come work for me.
I don't work
for nobody.
It's too bad, Dubois.
It's too bad.
You're a wasted-talent
nutcase, you know that?
Suit yourself.
I got money to make.
Move.
Hey, here.
Please, juggle.
Dubois, I want you and
your kids off the street.
I mean it, Dubois.
This is it.
Move it, kid.
Watch it.
Get down now
or we'll knock you flat.
Grab him!
Some nut, huh?
Yeah.
Get your ass
down here.
Dubois, get down.
You've crossed
the line, Dubois.
Hey, what are
you doing?
Looking for a toilet.
There's no toilet there.
Get lost. Get lost.
Where'd he go?
Did you get it?
There was
nothing there.
It's impossible.
Today's the day.
Nothing, Chief.
Sorry.
Nothing? Nothing.
I don't believe it.
Wow!
Did I
tell you or what? We're rich!
Yeah!
Look at that!
With this, we buy respect.
If we want something,
we take it.
Forever and ever.
Forever and ever!
Billy.
Yes, Chief?
Get us some food.
Some real food.
Go.
Let's celebrate.
Yeah!
Good night.
I'm so full
I could bust.
Red, you go to bed. See
you in the morning, kids.
Dubois!
Hand me the dough, clown,
or the kid's dead.
Easy,easy. The kid had
nothing to do with it.
Shut your mouth
and hand me the bag!
You heard him,
Dubois. Hand it over.
Count it.
Nobody steals from me.
Nobody.
Billy.
Oh, Billy.
It's okay. It's okay.
He's gonna be fine.
The cops are gonna
blame you, Chris.
Chris. Chris!
They're gonna kill you!
Get outta here! Go!
Red, you're in charge now. No matter
what happens, I'll come back.
I swear to God.
I'll come back.
This way!
Down here!
Put them in the wagon.
All right,
come with me.
Dubois! I'm gonna find you
and I'm gonna kill you!
Dubois! Dubois!
Check the exits! Watch the docks!
He's here somewhere!
Move it! Check under the girders!
Dubois!
Check the cargo. Look
around those boxes.
What was that?
By the warehouse!
Move out!
Check the two bins
there.
Check the cargo bay.
Under there.
Keep moving.
Your mother's health isn't
improving, and her money's gone.
I rather doubt
she'll be coming.
Now, Christopher, be a good
boy and stay right here.
I'll be back.
Don't move.
Don't move!
What is this?
A stowaway.
You'll work for us.
Put him in chains.
Wait.
Come on.
Back to work.
I come to say goodbye.
It's a shame,
but even good things
come to an end.
Yes. I'm sure
the sharks will enjoy you.
Hit the boiler room.
Grappling irons, now!
Cast!
Fire at Will!
Come on, boys.
The Turk's ours.
Harry,
who the hell's that?
We're even.
Hey, you're losing
your aim, Dobbsy.
What's your name, son?
Christopher Dubois.
Mine's Dobbs.
Lord Dobbs.
And how can we be of
service, Christopher Dubois?
I need to find a ship
back to America.
America, eh?
Well, you're in luck.
We might just find one
on Muay Thai Island.
Muay Thai Island?
No...
Trust me.
Yes, sir.
You are now the guest of Admiral
Dobbs and Harry Smithe.
The last of the buccaneers.
Come aboard.
Thanks.
Piece of shit.
Muay Thai Island
off the bow!
Muay Thai Island, Chris.
Where my good friend Mr.
Khao will take care of you.
Hurry it up, lads.
Quickly as you can
with those boxes, boys.
I want to get this tide
out of here.
Khao, my old friend.
Nice to see you.
How are you?
How's business?
That good, eh'?
Well, I have a few interesting
items I picked up on the way here.
Perfect for
insurrections.
But I have something
even better.
Harry. Bring Chris
over here.
Come on.
Watch the way
the boy moves.
Chris Dubois from the
United States of America,
the best fighter
I've ever seen.
Oh, Chris. Khao here was
saying he's going to make sure
you catch the boat that comes
here from the States next month.
Dobbsy...
Yes. Khao,
I suggest we step inside.
Dobbsy, boat?
Wait here, kid. We're gonna fix you
up nice with our friends here.
It's daylight
bloody robbery.
He could get killed in the first
fight, Dobbsy. Then what do I have?
But the boy is good. I've seen him fight.
Have I ever lied to you?
This is the offer.
Take it or leave it.
Hey, kid! Kid!
This is gonna turn out
to be your lucky day.
Great news, Chris.
There is a ship due in two
weeks, and you are on it.
No need to thank us.
Remember what I told you.
Watch out for your tail.
Watch my tail.
Harry.
How many weeks?
This is great.
Dobbsy, this is gonna be
the best one we ever had.
I do hate long goodbyes.
Be ready at all times.
You will learn that.
Or you'll never become
Muay Thai fighter.
I need some help.
Take me home.
And take care of Billy,
Red, the kids.
Hey. Leave him alone.
Yeah. Always be ready.
Well.
Forget it, Dobbs.
£50 says I can gain her
most intimate confidence.
Come on, Dobbs.
Trust me, Harry.
Waiter?
Yes, sir.
The young lady
who just came in,
would you ask her if she'd care to
partake of a flute of champagne?
Say it came from...
Lord Dobbs?
Yes, sir. Castle in Scotland,
factories in Singapore.
Smart lad.
Thank you.
Castle in Scotland?
Excuse me, miss.
The gentleman over there
would like to see you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. Do we
know one another?
I can't be sure,
Miss...
Newton.
Miss Newton.
Maybe it was
my castle in Scotland
or our vineyards
in the south of France?
No.
No matter. I shall
remember, Miss Newton.
By the way,
I'm Lord Edgar Dobbs,
and this is the president of my
company, Harry Smithe, with an
Ma'am.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Carrie Newton.
Miss Carrie Newton.
Will you join us?
Well, I just came in
for some refreshment.
Well, then, take it
with us, please.
All right.
Thank you, my Lord.
Edgar
Let's dispense
with silly titles.
So, what brings you to the
Orient, if I may inquire?
I'm here
on assignment.
On assignment?
Like a journalist?
Yes.
The New York Globe.
New York Globe, huh?
Hmm.
Maybe we met
through my father.
Your father?
Howard Newton.
He owns The Globe.
Oh, yes, a splendid chap.
They do say you can
buy anything you desire
on the streets
of Bangkok.
And what is it
you desire, Lord Dobbs?
A great number of things,
but what about you, my dear?
Well, what
any woman desires.
Oh?
A great story.
What's he saying?
Harry?
Something about Muay
Thai tournament tonight.
Fighting or something.
That's what I desire.
Brutality?
Strictly for the peasants.
I am a journalist.
All right.
Harry will arrange it.
Noisy, isn't it?
Yeah.
I warned you
it was for peasants.
We'll get a seat
over here.
Dobbs!
Khao.
What a lovely surprise.
You are a thief, Dobbs.
You sold me
rusty rifles.
Nothing that
a little oil won't cure.
Nice American lady.
A very important journalist.
Carrie Newton. Very good
friend of Lord Dobbs.
Might write nice things
about Muay Thai fighting.
Make you famous in the
United States of America.
Oh, I see. It's my
pleasure to meet you.
Please, have a seat up there
with my good friend Lord Dobbs.
My God.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Let's go.
You have to
get me this story.
I'll arrange it.
Did you see him?
Yes, of course I saw him.
Just keep moving.
Did you see him?
Keep moving.
Chris.
We were looking for you,
weren't we?
Yeah, we were
looking for you.
Good to
see you again, my boy.
You've put on
a little muscle.
You've become famous. I
always said you'd make it.
Didn't I?
Mmm-hmm.
You owe me.
Yes, I do, Chris, and I
always repay my debts.
What do you want?
The golden dragon.
Golden what?
The golden dragon
in the Lost City.
Lost City?
The best fighters will
meet to compete in secret
for a big dragon
made of solid gold.
Solid gold.
You think you can win?
No.
You're learning.
What exactly
do you want me to do?
You buy me back from Khao and
finance my trip to the Lost City.
Carrie Newton.
What'd I miss?
Chris, my son, it is fortuitous,
us meeting like this.
A bloody gold dragon, eh?
Well, I'll tell you what.
You get us to the Lost City,
and I'll make sure that you...
We come back
with the gold dragon.
Deal.
Yeah, Newman,
I got it.
No, it's "Newton."
N-E-W-T-O-N.
Do you have a table?
Lord Dobbs.
It's all right,
waiter. He's with us.
I need a way
to get on the journey.
Find your own, lady.
Well, how about at least
printing a teaser on the story?
Okay, you get me a photo, and I
might get it in "Around the World."
Wait. Here's the wire.
Aren't you the one we sent to the
Orient to get out of our hair?
Hello! Hey, Newman, you there?
Oh, my God.
Hello!
You see, Chris,
the problem is that you can't get
into this wretched Ghan-gheng thing
without
a special invitation.
We'll forge it.
Impossible.
Apparently, it has
a map on it,
so we are faced
with a real dilemma.
Good morning,
gentlemen.
Miss Newton.
What are you
so cheerful about?
Because, my Lord, I hold in my
hand your ticket to that journey.
Not so fast.
First we make a deal.
What kind of deal?
I go with you
to the Ghan-gheng.
How do we know
it's good?
Oh, it's good.
It's very good.
Without it,
your plans are worthless.
That's me. Devine. I need some help.
Come with me.
Mr. Devine?
That's me.
Welcome to Bangkok.
I am Edgar Dobbs of the
Ghan-gheng committee.
This is Harry Smithe and Christopher
Dubois, your personal valet.
Hey, this is great. I thought
I was gonna get stuck
with a couple of little Oriental
fellas didn't speak no English.
Not for you, Champ.
Chris, the bags.
Dobbs, I'm gonna kill you.
Not yet. Remember,
it's thieves with pride that
dangle from the gallows.
Who said that?
Edgar Dobbs,
Ivory Coast, 1920.
Besides, Chris, my son, we
have an almost perfect plan.
Maxie has the map
and the invitation
that are going to
get us into the Lost City.
All that will be
on his mind is fighting.
Miss Newton is off getting
her story of the century
and in the meantime, you,
Harry and yours truly
will be devising ways and
means of stealing the Dragon.
Yeah.
Sounds good to me.
Good?
It is perfect.
All we have to do is keep
the champ in our pocket.
So, we ready to go?
Thank you.
Well, now,
who is this?
Carrie Newton.
It's a pleasure to meet the
Heavyweight Champion of the World.
Is she going with us?
Somebody's got to record
this historic event.
Let's get going-
Her father owns
the New York Globe.
Well, whoop-de-doo.
All right, everybody,
let's make
a pretty picture.
Smile.
Come on. Smile!
Now what?
Trust me.
Man, boss, these
elephants are busting my rump.
Oh, stop
complaining, Harry.
We could be back
in Cairo on camels.
Where'd you get the haircut?
The army?
No, I'm... I'm a sailor.
I'll tell you what. You look like
you're in pretty good shape.
I'll work you out, give you
a few pointers. Who knows?
Maybe you'd make
a good fighter.
Now that's the way
to earn some money.
Yeah.
Yep, that's a pretty lady.
Oh, my aching rump.
Elephants.
From now on in,
it's horses.
Dobbs. I'm gonna
go for a walk.
Be careful, boyo.
Taking one?
A funeral.
No headstones. That's how
they bury thieves here.
Makes them
give back to the earth.
Hey, Dobbs, what do you
drink with tonic?
Don't tell me.
Gin.
I said don't tell me.
Shut up, you!
The Americans!
Welcome to
our humble inn.
Thank you.
What the hell is this?
Fresh-killed
cobra, Champ.
Well, I always say one should
never eat on an empty stomach.
I'm for that.
Well, isn't this
a small world?
Khao, my old friend, I just
realized I owed you some money.
Harry?
You didn't pay him?
No, he didn't pay me. He's a thief.
I'm used to him.
But you...
You are worse.
You'll dare go to the
Ghan-gheng to fight against us,
after we've trained you in the
ways of the Muay Thai warrior.
You got it all wrong, pops.
He ain't gonna fight. I am.
Correct.
That is correct. This is
Maxie Devine, the Champ.
You are a fighter?
What are
you talking about?
What the hell's
going on here?
He's just talking nonsense.
Don't take any notice.
It's gone awful
quiet in here, hasn't it?
Now, as I was saying,
before I was so rudely
interrupted by Mr. Khao,
who doesn't know his
armpit from his elbow...
Excuse me, honorable sir.
We need this table.
So do we.
But we...
You heard him!
Now beat it.
I said...
I said,
"Do you speak English?"
He knows
what you're saying.
Hey, pal, scram.
Easy, kid.
It ain't worth it.
What the hell is this?
That's what you'll face
at the Ghan-gheng.
Good morning, Champ.
Good morning, my ass. You
think I was born yesterday?
You don't have anything to do with
this damn Ghan-gheng, do you?
Huh? And you're
no valet, either.
You're nothing but
a cheap, lying punk.
Take it easy.
Take it easy?
You ain't no fighter, either. You
wouldn't last one round in a real fight.
What do you think
of that?
Hey.
You want some?
Come on. Come on!
Maxie.
No more.
Is this what
you're after?
So what are you
looking so glum about?
"Maxie Devine."
This is Maxie Devine,
Champion of America.
Welcome to Ghan-gheng.
Kishu Yama from Japan.
Phang Prahan of Siam.
I am Phang.
Maxie Devine
of America.
That's me.
Maxie Devine, Heavyweight
Champion of the World.
This man is a better
fighter than me,
and as the former
Heavyweight Champion,
I turn my title
over to him.
This here's your man,
Christopher Dubois.
Dubois will be
granted a chance
to prove if he is a worthy
combatant in the first round.
If not, Maxie Devine
shall pay the penalty
and never leave
the Lost City.
That thing
is bigger than I thought.
Why did you come back?
I've been champion
a long time,
and you beat me, with your
legs and with your speed.
Besides, when I got the
invitation to come here
I decided I was gonna see the American
flag flying at the end of this thing.
I don't know
what's on your mind, Chris,
but I do know a champion
when I meet one,
and I'm here to see
that you fight like one.
Now you know why.
Here in the Lost City,
at the top of the world,
we greet our first heroes.
In this mystical arena,
there are no masks,
just truth.
I wish you well.
Soviet Union against Spain.
Damn.
Japan against Okinawa.
France against Brazil.
China against Korea.
He's moving
like an animal.
More like a snake.
Harry, our little
pension fund.
Yeah.
Hey, boss, how come there ain't
nobody watching this thing?
Well, 'cause they don't
think anybody can lift it.
All right, let's see
what you got.
Come on. Let's go.
Chris, how are
you feeling?
The kid's a winner.
Of course he is,
for at least one round.
I mean,
for your sake.
After all, you don't
want to become
a permanent resident
of the Lost City, do you?
You should be
in training.
I know you're gonna
win the first round.
Yeah.
You're gonna win
the whole thing.
You gonna split
the prize with them?
We have a deal.
So do we.
Turkey against Scotland.
Siam against Africa.
Germany against
United States.
Chris, now, I don't
know about you,
but I plan on seeing
Times Square again.
Get him!
He's outclassed.
Hope you enjoy Christmas
in the Lost City.
New York City!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Mongolia against Greece.
This guy's
no big deal.
Japan against Turkey.
Now he's got a style
like a monkey.
Mongolia against Siam.
It's over.
Hit the gong!
No!
Phang.
Chris, sit down!
Chris?
We need a little chat.
Okay.
Tomorrow you are
throwing the fight.
Throwing the...
Taking a dive.
A plunge, kid.
You see, it is
the perfect setup.
But that dragon
is so bloody enormous,
if we're going to lift it out
of here, we need you healthy.
Well, let's face it.
You have been lucky so far.
Why the long face?
I thought this was
your quest, your dream.
Well, soon
it'll be a reality.
Harry, I think the kid
needs some rest.
Sleep well.
Spain against
United States.
Up. Get up!
Get up!
Yeah! How about that? The kid
can really take a beating.
It's time
for plan B.
What's plan B?
Semifinal.
Mongolia against Japan.
See, the winner's
gonna wear himself out,
then he'll roll
right over for you.
This is good.
Lucky punch.
Yeah.
Yeah. Lucky punch.
Come on, Dobbsy!
Dobbs, come on!
Come on. Dobbs!
Come on!
Secure it!
Semifinal.
United States against China.
Tiger.
Hurry it up!
I can't hold this forever!
Yeah! All right, Dobbs!
Is it secure?
Yeah! What about me?
Come on!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, Dobbs!
You bastard!
What about me?
I'll see you
outside the gates.
Trust me, Harry.
Dobbs, we got company.
Run for it, Harry!
Dobbs!
What a mess.
Oh, yeah?
I'm sorry, kid, we
tried to run out on you.
I guess that's the
difference between us.
I never ever said I was
sorry before and meant it.
And I never ever
had a quest
that wasn't for me,
number one.
I wasn't always
a pirate, you know.
Believe it or not,
for over 20 years I was a genuine
captain in the Royal Navy.
I raised the Union Jack in
countries you never even heard of,
fought the Hun
in the Great War.
For what?
For the glory of God, the British
Empire and His Majesty the King.
And when it was all over,
what was I left with?
Oh, well, you win some,
you lose some.
Now, you just watch
your tail, my old son.
These men have
committed a great sacrilege
against this competition.
Let it be known that the
price for such betrayal
is death.
No!
I will pay
for their freedom.
I brought them here.
It's my fault.
If I win,
they'll go free.
You'll keep the Dragon.
This is for good.
So be it.
Final event.
Mongolia against
United States.
Cover up!
Yeah!
Chris!
Get up!
Chris! Get up!
Come on.
We're dead, Dobbs.
We're dead!
I won't say it again, Harry.
Shut up!
Chris!
Chris, give yourself
some room!
Chris!
Boss, this don't
sound good.
Don't sound
good at all.
At least while they're shouting,
it means he's still alive.
Chris, you got him! Now get
in there and finish him!
Go, go, go!
Yeah!
Come on!
You've done it!
Chris!
Chris! Chris! Chris!
Chris, it's me,
Maxie! Chris!
It's all right, kid.
You did it.
Christopher
Dubois, we honor you
as the greatest warrior
of the Ghan-gheng.
Hey, way to go, Champ-
Thanks.
Christopher, now that you are
the undisputed champion,
I've been thinking.
About what?
A plan.
A perfect plan.
I don't think he wants to
hear about it now, Harry.
I didn't get
the golden dragon,
but I returned to New
York, like I promised,
got the kids
off the streets.
In the end,
we all did just fine.
Maxie trained many great fighters
and became a big celebrity.
Last I heard, Dobbs and Harry opened
a trading post deep in the Amazon.
Bless their souls.